studentready.com 2011-11-03

# Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy

##  What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When completing a transaction on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other personal information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

##  What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience
  * To improve our website
  * To process transactions
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic email

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive email that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future email, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

##  How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you complete a transaction.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive personal information is transmitted into our database to be accessed only by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, who are required to keep the information confidential.

##  Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enable the site or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf, except to help us conduct and improve our business.

##  Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies or protect ours or others rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

##  Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

##  Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

##  Changes to our privacy policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the privacy policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on May 3, 2011.

##  Contacting us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below:

www.studentready.com

P.O. Box 30001

Austin, TX 78755

privacy@studentready.com
